{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Many women and children were walking down the street, but ___.",
      "a": "scanty men",
      "b": "little of men",
      "c": "few men",
      "d": "a little number of men",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- few + countable nouns",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ of us will wait here.",
      "a": "A fewer",
      "b": "Some",
      "c": "Much",
      "d": "A little",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Some of us",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "She spent ___ on her new coat.",
      "a": "quite a little money",
      "b": "money quite a little",
      "c": "quite little money",
      "d": "little money quite",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Quite + a(n) + adj + noun",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "This club has a large _________ of girls.",
      "a": "lot",
      "b": "amount",
      "c": "number",
      "d": "many",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- A large number of + noun: a quantity of people or things",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "I weigh 65kg and you weigh 65kg. We are ___ weight.",
      "a": "same heavy",
      "b": "as heavy as",
      "c": "as heavy",
      "d": "of the same",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Of the same weight (of + adj + n) = be same in weight",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "A ___ reader does not understand science books written for experts.",
      "a": "young",
      "b": "foolish",
      "c": "lay",
      "d": "careless",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Lay:Â not trained or not knowing much about a particular profession or subject.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "That's a very nice skirt you're wearing. \"Thank you. I'm glad ___ \"",
      "a": "liked it by you",
      "b": "you to like it",
      "c": "to be liked by you",
      "d": "you like it",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Be glad (that) + a clause",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "The men at the lunch counter ordered ___ and two platters of fried shrimp.",
      "a": "three black coffees",
      "b": "some three black coffee",
      "c": "black three coffees",
      "d": "black three coffee",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Word order: quantity (one, two, three etc...) - colours (red, blue, green ...) - nouns",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "He was surprised to read the passage at the end of ___.",
      "a": "five chapter",
      "b": "chapter five",
      "c": "fifth chapter",
      "d": "chapter the fifth",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Chapter five (= the fifth chapter)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is this camera cheap? \"It is not _________ what we paid.\"",
      "a": "value",
      "b": "cost",
      "c": "worthy",
      "d": "worth",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Be worth something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "5"
    }
  ]
}